### Fiqri Ardiansyah

## Frontend Dev At Crealoka | External Code Reviewer At Dicoding

I have experience in front end web development, have worked in startups before and am now an internal programmer at a company in Jakarta, Indonesia.

will continue to expand knowledge especially in the field of front end.

Let's make something beautiful with code!

Medan, Indonesia
085273580367
fiqriardian92@gmail.com
https://www.linkedin.com/in/fiqr
i-ardiansyah-a48651190/
https://fiqri-ardiansyah.vercel.app

#### **Experience**

Maret 2022 - Present Jakarta, Indonesia

#### Frontend Developer

#### Crealoka

- -Create and maintaining dashboard application for internal use
- -Build other side applications
  -Integration with backend API

Juni 2021 - Maret 2022 Jakarta, Indonesia

# Frontend Developer Panggilin

- -Maintain and fix existing web application bugs
- -Added new features to the web application
- -Create and Maintain other side application

#### **Projects**

#### Jrg Bus

Jasa rahayu gumpueng - Aceh, Indonesia

Build a dashboard web application from the frontend side that is used by Rahayu Gumpueng Bus Services for internal administration purposes

#### Monapro

Telkom Indonesia - Jakarta, Indonesia

Create a dashboard for Telkom Indonesia's internal needs.

#### **Education**

2019 - 2023

#### Universitas Mikroskil Teknik Informatika

#### **Skills**

- Javascript
- TypeScript
- React.js
- Next.js
- PWA(Progressive Web App)
- Redux